[Music]
so today i went back to my old one room
cottage
the reason for that is the little garden
next to it has been replanted with
potatoes and there were quite a few of
my plants that i wanted to rescue from
being tilled so i came to pick them up
and got an opportunity to look around
and see inside and how it is being
changed and renovated
it is no doubt going to look lovely and
it was interesting walking through and
having such bittersweet emotions so much
has changed since i left this little
house only five months ago
i'm proud of myself for having loved
that cottage and also being able to know
when it was time to move on
[Music]
so
yes
[Music]
later that day i had to drive into my
little town for my weekend job at the
bookstore it is buzzing with tourism
right now and the shop has been so busy
i've been able to meet some of you there
so please always feel free to stop by
and say hello
i will be available for a book signing
once my book is released in august so i
will leave the dates down below if you'd
like to stop by
[Music]
if you have any books you've loved this
year please let me know i've been trying
to read even more than usual
writing my own book has been such a
wonderful process and i'm hoping in the
future i will have the chance to write
more i would love to make a children's
book and illustrate it i would also love
to write novels in the future
also i've been trying to expand my
reading genres thanks to a co-worker of
mine
besides my recent more fairy tale reads
such as these i've been attempting to
read books on spookier topics some have
been a bit too scary but i have enjoyed
detective stories recently
[Music]
back home i've been trying to get my
garden finally in order the area is
quite wild but there's still a
surprising amount of lovely flowers
growing all over the place
so i thought i would give you a very
quick garden tour so you can see what
i've been up to
apologies for the shaky camera here we
have growing a huge amount of different
flowers primarily larkspur calendula
iris cornflower honeysuckle chamomile
also various edible wildflowers and
herbs for teas and recipes
as you can see this area is quite wild
and free there are a lot of weeds and
other flowers mixed into what i
intentionally planted i'm kind of going
to keep it that way for now i love the
wild look and i also want to encourage
the growth and abundance of native
plants on the property
luke is gonna build me a lovely little
fenced area where i can let my cat
safely enjoy the outdoors
and i'm so excited to see how things
evolve and develop over time
my mother-in-law has planted a lot of
flowers here over the years
so a lot of the work hasn't been done by
me for sure i'm so grateful for her and
her eye for beauty
as for vegetables i'm growing lettuce
carrots radish peppers beets peas and
tomatoes i don't have much space yet so
it will be a small harvest but i'm
grateful to have this space
so yes i think in another year or two
things will look quite different but all
these things take time especially when
it comes to plants
so i will update you as things go
on a final note revisiting my thoughts
on my old cottage
i hope that whenever you're faced with
fear of the unknown or change or growth
in general
know that most anything worth having is
always at risk of being lost
and growing and developing over time
means making mistakes and learning to
let go where needed
and finding courage to face scary yet
exciting opportunities
for me it was always a question of
balance
enjoying a quiet comfortable life while
still pushing myself in small ways to
continue to grow and develop as a person
in this case it meant leaving my cottage
for a new chapter and so far it has been
so worth it
[Music]
hello everyone i hope you're all doing
well i just got back home and got
changed and refreshed after going to my
old cottage
and it was a really interesting
experience to spend some time walking
around
i'd not actually been inside since i
left and so
it was really
lovely and thought provoking to spend a
little bit of time there and think about
how in so little time
so much has changed
and it's a really funny feeling
especially when it really only has been
i think about five months at this point
it was um still felt kind of odd and
different to go back and
see my garden transformed and so much of
the house being transformed and
renovated and so i think moments like
that are always a little bit bittersweet
because you have so many lovely memories
associated with your home where you
lived
and you have not yet had adequate time
to build up all your new memories and
experiences of years in your new house
at the same time i am so happy and
strangely proud of myself to have the
courage to move forward and make choices
that i wanted to make even though they
scared me and so that is something that
i've been thinking about quite a bit
right now but yes walking through the
old house got me thinking a lot about
how for so many years i really let fear
rather dictate my decisions you know i
was very um fearful of stepping outside
of my comfort zone in any way i noticed
especially at my old job in the city
i felt very kind of overwhelmed with
life in general and i was having a lot
of anxiety the reason for my anxiety
wasn't my location it was just me ex you
know me still not being able to quite
learn how to adult and manage and
process my feelings and at one point i
was so anxious about life in general
that i pretty much
got on the bus went to work worked for
10 hours
got on the bus again and came home
and would just stay in my room and i
would do that day in and day out and day
in and day out and even though i'm quite
an introverted person and i love to
spend days alone in my room and i
certainly really need my alone time you
know i was noticing that in my personal
case my world was getting smaller and
smaller and smaller i was so comfortable
with my very limited routine that
i wasn't even giving the opportunity for
new people to come into my life
especially positive people
and the more i stayed at home the more
kind of comfortable i got with my
routine to the point that i was fearful
of any changes for the first time i
would suddenly start feeling social
anxiety and anxiety associated with new
people or relationships and all of those
new things became unwelcomed because
they
meant facing a lot of my fears
associated with being rejected not
measuring up to someone else's standards
if i kept avoiding all these fears of
failure and of not succeeding in the
things that i want to do
i might as well just
accept that in my life i'm not going to
try to do anything at all decision to
finally make a change and to start
facing fears and treating that emotion
of fear and anxiety as something that
had to be understood and worked with
instead of avoid it altogether and so
that was really important for me but
anyway i hope you have a wonderful week
sending you all my love
and i will see you soon goodbye
you